freebieslove.com 2015-05-11

# Privacy Policy

At **[www.freebieslove.com/](http://www.freebieslove.com/ "Freebies Love")** , we are dedicated to protecting the privacy of our customers. As testimony to our commitment in this regard, we use an extensive privacy policy, detailed as under.

Please note that the privacy policy is subject to change without any prior notice, and any such alteration becomes effective immediately after appearing on this page. ****

 **[www.freebieslove.com/](http://www.freebieslove.com/ "Freebies Love")** strictly adheres to the privacy principles laid down by the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) for websites that collect personally identifying information

  * ##  ** _Information Collection_**

  * ###  **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

This refers to the information that does not personally identify users, and includes information such as your IP address, the Domain Name, Browser Type, Operating System, Country of Origin, Time of Visit, Navigation and Click-Stream data; and is collected for site activity analysis. ****

  * ### Personally Identifiable Information

  1. This refers to information that can be used to personally identify users, such as their names, email address and web site.
  2. This type of information is collected at few points in the website enumerated as under
  3. Registration for our email subscription services requires the mandatory submission of name and email address.
  4. Posting comments on any part of our website requires the user’s name and email address (compulsory) and their website address (optional).
  5. Additional information may be collected upon contacting our Customer Support department.

  * ###  **Personal Information Security**

We do not share your personal information with any third parties, and work our level best in safe guarding your privacy.[](http://www.freestuffresort.com/)

 **[www.freebieslove.com/](http://www.freebieslove.com/ "Freebies Love")** maintains industry standards while storing user information, including the use of powerful encryption and firewalls.

Only our employees are granted access to this information as they require it so as to fulfill their job responsibilities. ** __**

  * ##  **Information Usage**

  * ###  **Non-personally identifiable information may be used to**

  1. Analyze site activity, and making offers that are more relevant to our user demographic.

  * ###  **Personally Identifiable Information may be used to**

  1. Provide requested customer support to our users
  2. Trouble shooting
  3. Preventing illegal activities, and enforcing our Terms of Use and site policy
  4. Offering updates and upgrades to our customers through the web site and blog via our customers’ email addresses

  * ## Information Disclosure

User information is used only by our technical and administrative staff. Under no circumstances is it ever sold, rented out to or shared with third parties.

However, exceptions to the above occur in the event of a court order or under the directive of a Government body. ** __**

  * ##  **Links to Other Websites**

Given the nature of the services offered by [**w** **ww.freebieslove.com/**](http://www.freebieslove.com/ "Freebies Love"), the website possesses links to numerous third party websites.

We are, in no way connected to the individual privacy policies of the respective third party websites, nor are we responsible for any breach of privacy that may occur upon visiting them.

Once you leave [**www.freebieslove.com** /](http://www.freebieslove.com/ "Freebies Love") by clicking on a link to a third party website, we accept no liability for any information that may be collected- with or without your consent- and the storage, use and disclosure of such information.

Therefore, we urge you to carefully read the privacy policies of each third party website that you choose to visit.

Please feel free to contact us should you have any queries regarding this privacy policy.
